# **Armando Peña**

## **FullStack Developer**



+53

+53 51705953

 $\bowtie$ 

arm and o.pen a@ntsprint.com



armandodev.vercel.app



Banes, Holguín (Cuba)

## **EXPERIENCE**

2024 - Present FullStack Web Developer

**NTSprint** 

Worked with, Angular, Lumen, Squidex, and Keycloak. performance and SEO, added Cypress end-to-end testing, custom search service, caching systems, and design patterns.

2023 - 2023 FrontEnd Web Developer

**Cuban Engineer** 

Website made with Angular with landing page, profile manager and CV creator. Upgraded Angular from version 10 to 15. Worked on performance improvements.

2023 - 2023 FrontEnd Web Developer

Wassermeloni

Website made with Angular and Ruby on Rails. Upgraded the Angular version from version 10 to 15. Worked on performance and security improvements.

2019 - 2023 **Mobile Developer** 

**Imagined Earth** 

Mobile SaaS application made with Ionic, Angular and Laravel, migrated to AWS. Added advertising, wallet, Google Maps integration and costs improvements, and user rewards. Deployed on Google Play and Apps Store.

## **EDUCATION**

2022- 2022 **Computer Sciences** 

**Harvard CS50x** 

I learned C and Python with an amazing staff.

2009 - 2013 **Software Engineer** 

**University of Informatic Sciences** 

I learned software engineering and web development.

## REFERENCES

Alián Rigñack CEO at CE

CEO at CE

**E:** alian@aleph.engineering

Alvaro Raul Developer

**P:** +53 56839233

E: melkor@aleph.engineering

## **STATEMENT**

I'm a Software Engineer specializing in FullStack web development. I mainly have experience with Angular and Node.js. I enjoy collaborating with teams and strive to write clean, and efficient code. I'm also interested in Game Development using Unity, and creating engaging digital experiences. I love to stay updated with the latest web development trends and share my learnings on my blog.

## **SKILLS**

## **Professional**

HTML/CSS3

JavaScript

TypeScript

Angular

Node.js

#### **Personal**

Perfectionist
Communication
Hard Work

## **FOLLOW ME**

#### Medium

https://medium.com/@armanp

### Twitter(X)

https://twitter.com/arman2p284

## Linkedin

/in/armando-pe%C3%B1a-7622bb20a/